Handling books with care.
Is it important?
Oh, it is so so very very important.
These books are old books that I have and I treasure them and my child or any child that would come into the house would see oh, there's mommy's or daddy's, one of their favorite books.
The way I treated the book says a lot that I care about reading.
Where, if I had something like this laying around or certain books that I may use for classes that's all ripped up, marked, what's that telling your child?
You don't care.
And if you don't care, they learn not to care.
For example, if before I go out, if I have to fix my hair or fix my jewelry or make sure my watch looks nice, that's showing the child that I care how I look.
How you keep your books, your newspapers and any type of literature in your home, tells the child and awful awful lot.
Today we have a lot of CDs, DVDs, and if you show you care or how they're displayed, your child will learn.
We can teach so much more, not by talking and preaching, but by modeling good behavior for our child.
So please, books are a treasure and handle them and show that you care and they are your treasure.